Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Drama alumni records, 1932-1968; Series III
  - Drama Alumni Association: Executive Committee, 1948-1952 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, 1955-1968 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Financial Reports, 1955-1965 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - General Information Sheets, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - President, 1962-1971 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Social Events, 1959-1968 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Talent Directory-First Edition, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Talent Directory-Second Edition, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Talent Directory-Third Edition, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - West Coast, 1961-1964 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Gifts to Dept. of Drama
    - 1925-1926 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Portraits, 1926-1945 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Gifts (Old), 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Playwrights, Alumni, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Prospective Donors, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Report of the Survey Committee on Alumni of Graduate and Professional Schools, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Students, Ex- Activities, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Students, List of Former (Present Activities), 1927-1949 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Students in Service and Alumni Information, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Yale Drama Alumni Newsletter
    - 1955-1959 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - 1960-1968 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Edward Cole files, 1923-1970; Series IV
  - Acoustics, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - General Articles, 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Seminars, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - The Architectural Record, 1933-1939 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Articles on Theatre Design, 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Arts and the Government, 1952-1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Arts in Secondary Education: The Putney School, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - The Arts and the Press: Conference, University of Texas, Austin, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Civil Defense, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class Schedules, 1942-1965 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - C-Note Club, 1956-1960 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Consultant: Cazenovia College, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Consultant: University of Illinois, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Commencement, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Concessions, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Contracts, 1936-1940 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Copyrights, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Curriculum: D.F.A. Directing, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Curriculum: Theatre Design and Technology, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Proposals, 1934-1935 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Department of Health, Educaton and Welfare, 1956-1964 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Drama 131
    - 1939-1941 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Scenery, Advanced Problems, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Problems for Study, circa 1940s (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Bibliography, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Production Manager, Duties of, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Theatre Planning, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Rigging Systems, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Sound, 1959-1962 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Stage Equipment, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Research Topics, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Drama 131: Research Topics, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Class Topics, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Homework and Tests, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Eastern Press, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Eaves Award (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Entering Class Lists, 1925-1942 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Exhibit and Slides, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1933 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Minutes
    - 1946-1956 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - 1956-1965 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Faculty: Non-Alumni, 1955-1971 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Fellowships in other Schools, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Film Rental
    - 1937-1949 (Box 43, Folder 65)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 66)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 43, Folder 67)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 68)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 69)
    - 1962 (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Films: "It's Not All Play", 1947 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - Finances, 11928-1934 (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - Freedly, George: New York Public Library, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - Samuel French, Inc., 1955 (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - General Information Sheets for Those Beginning Careers in Professional Theatre, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - Goodfriend and Associates: Acoustics, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Grade Sheets, 1951-1966 (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Guggenheim Museum, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - H Correspondence, 1942-1963 (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Improvements: Yale University Theatre, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Improvements and Maintenance, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Improvements: Yale University Theatre
    - 1956-1959 (Box 44, Folder 84)
    - 1957 (Box 44, Folder 85)
    - 1958 (Box 44, Folder 86)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 87)
    - 1962 (Box 44, Folder 88)
    - 1964 (Box 44, Folder 89)
    - Long-Range, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Inspection of Theatre, Certificates of, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 91)
  - Institute of Theatre Technology (ITT), 1961-1966 (Box 44, Folder 92)
    - Code Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 44, Folder 93)
    - Committee on Administration, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 94)
    - Executive Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 95)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 45, Folder 96)
    - General, 1961-1969 (Box 45, Folder 97)
    - Theatre Administration, 1961-1967 (Box 45, Folder 98)
    - Theatre Architecture, 1961-1964 (Box 45, Folder 99)
  - ITT: Theatre Engineering, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 100)
    - 1961-1964 (Box 45, Folder 101)
    - Theatrical Presentation, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 102)
  - International Copyright Bureau, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 103)
  - James Jewell: Drama Teaching, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 105)
  - K Correspondence, 1954-1964 (Box 45, Folder 107)
  - Jay Keene: Sound Isolation, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 108)
  - Lincoln Center, 1956-1966 (Box 45, Folder 110)
  - Lists of Directors, Actors, Technicians, 1956-1979 (Box 45, Folder 111)
  - M Correspondence, 1943-1964 (Box 46, Folder 113)
  - Management, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 114)
  - James Miller: Theatre Planning, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 115)
  - Motion Pictures Theatre Design, 1932-1937 (Box 46, Folder 116)
  - Municipal Licenses, 1927-1948 (Box 46, Folder 117)
  - National Catholic Theatre Conference, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 119)
  - National Cultural Network, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 120)
  - NBC, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 121)
  - New England Regional Theater Assembly, 1950-1952 (Box 46, Folder 122)
  - New England Secondary School Drama Festival, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 123)
  - New England Speech Association, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 124)
  - New England Theatre Conference, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 125)
    - 1952-1960 (Box 46, Folder 126)
    - 1960-1968 (Box 46, Folder 127)
    - Programs, 1959-1968 (Box 47, Folder 128)
  - New Facilities: Faculty Recommendations, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 129)
  - New Haven Committee on Adult Education, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 130)
  - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1953-1955 (Box 47, Folder 131)
  - New Haven Drama Tournament Association, 1948-1949 (Box 47, Folder 132)
  - Operations Manuals, 1942-1965 (Box 47, Folder 133)
  - Outside: WWII Uses of Theatre, 1943-1946 (Box 47, Folder 134)
  - P Correspondence, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 135)
  - Personnel, 1960-1964 (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - Librarian, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 137)
    - Technicians, Staff, 1943-1950 (Box 47, Folder 138)
    - Theatre Custodian, 1944-1946 (Box 47, Folder 139)
  - Photography: Building and Equipment, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 140)
  - Procedures, 1933-1966 (Box 47, Folder 142 - 143)
  - Publications by Faculty, Alumni, Students, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 144)
  - Radio City Music Hall, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 145)
  - Red Buttons Show: CBS, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 146)
  - Regional Theatres: Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 147)
  - Reports, 1933-1948 (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Hilyard Robinson: Theatre Design, 1935-1936 (Box 48, Folder 149)
  - Joel Rubin: Outdoor Theatre, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - S Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 48, Folder 154)
  - Scenery Correspondence, 1934-1937 (Box 48, Folder 155)
    - 1937 (Box 48, Folder 156)
    - 1938-1949 (Box 48, Folder 157)
  - "The School Auditorium": Articles by Cole and McCandless, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 158)
  - Secondary School Theatre, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 159)
  - Shelter Magazine, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 160)
  - Social Functions, 1950-1956 (Box 48, Folder 161)
  - Sound, 1959-1963 (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - Sound System, 1955-1965 (Box 49, Folder 163)
  - Stage Equipment, 1957-1961 (Box 49, Folder 164)
  - Student Showcase, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 165)
  - Study for Hartt School Theatre (Article), 1951 (Box 49, Folder 166)
  - Syska and Hennessy: Theatre Design, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 167)
  - Theatre Design and Lighting (TDL): Evaluations, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 168)
    - Students, Third Year, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 169)
  - TDL Thesis: Progress Reports and Notes on Class Discussions, 1958-1961 (Box 49, Folder 170)
    - Quimsy Survey, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 171)
  - Technical Production: Drama 131 Field Trips, 1946-1954 (Box 49, Folder 172)
  - Theatre Arts Books, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 173)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 174)
  - Theatre Conference: Rules of Procedures, 1952-1953 (Box 49, Folder 175)
  - Theatre Design, 1925-1941 (Box 49, Folder 176)
  - Theatre Guild Fellowships, 1957-1969 (Box 49, Folder 177)
  - Theatre in Education, Inc., 1956 (Box 49, Folder 178)
  - Theatre Law: New Haven, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 179)
  - Theatre Planning, 1932-1960 (Box 49, Folder 180)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 181)
    - 1939-1949 (Box 50, Folder 182)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 50, Folder 183)
  - Tickets, 1927-1940 (Box 50, Folder 184)
  - U.S. International Information Administration, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 185)
  - V Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 50, Folder 186)
  - W Correspondence, 1949-1964 (Box 50, Folder 187)
  - Western Electric Co., 1949 (Box 50, Folder 189)
  - Yale Audio-visual Center, 1945-1950 (Box 50, Folder 192)
  - Yale Dramatic Association, 1925-1964 (Box 50, Folder 193)
  - Yale Studies for Returning Servicemen, 1925-1947 (Box 50, Folder 194)
  - Yale University Theatre Seats, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 195)
  - Yale University Treasurer's Office, 1951-1952 (Box 50, Folder 196)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 50, Folder 197)
- Faculty, 1928-1968; Series V
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
  - Biographies: G.P. Baker and Alexander Dean, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Costume Designers, 1926-1929 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Costume Instructors (Ex), 1925-1932 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Deanship, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Department
    - 1933 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 18 - 19)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 20 - 21)
    - 1940-1943 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - 1944-1946 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Departmental Exhibitional Material, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Folder, 1929-1944 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Faculty, 1964-1970 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Meeting Agenda, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Meetings
    - 1933-1936 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Memorandae, 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Minutes
    - 1933-1934 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - 1940-1954 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - 1942-1944 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - 1943-1946 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - 1946-1953 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - 1958-1966 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Faculty: Reports on Meetings, 1926-1933 (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Worksheets, 1925-1942 (Box 54, Folder 52 - 53)
  - Fox, James E., 1949 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Nagler, Afois, 1939-1948 (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Nagy, Elemer, 1939-1947 (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - New Faculty Appointments, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 81)
  - President, Reports to the
    - 1948-1958 (Box 55, Folder 84)
    - 1960-1965 (Box 55, Folder 85)
  - Press Releases, 1966-1968 (Box 55, Folder 86)
  - Requests for Leaves of Absence, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 88)
  - Resumes of Applicants for Teaching Positions, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 89)
  - Speeches and Magazine Articles by Faculty, undated (Box 56, Folder 95)
  - Thompson, Woodman, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 98)
- Finance records, 1926-1967; Series VI
  - Audience Reports, 1954-1965 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Bills: Receipted, 1939-1950 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Bills and Requests for Checks, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Budget Material, 1926-1930 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Building Maintenance, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Bursar, 1935-1949 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Bursary Appointments, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Business Management Schedule, 1948-1954 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Canfield, F. Curtis (Dean), Expenses (Income Tax), 1958-1963 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1956-1957 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Drama School Budgets, 1960-1966 (Box 57, Folder 13 - 14)
  - Estimates for Renovating the University Theatre, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Financial, 1931-1936 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements, 1957-1963 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Haskins and Sells: Yale Auditors, 1947-1950 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Inventory, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Inventories, 1929-1938 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Jobs, 1954-1959 (Box 58, Folder 23 - 24)
  - Job Applications, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Jobs, Inquiries Regarding, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Parking Permits, 1955-1960 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Personnel, 1955-1967 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Plant, Theatre, 1955-1957 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Production Budgets, 1954-1964 (Box 59, Folder 30 - 31)
  - Slides, Loans of and Charges, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Stage Manager, undated (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Statements of Account, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Statements of Expenses, 1956-1965 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Subscriptions, Reports on, 1962-1965 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Taxation, Committee on, 1926-1927 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Taxation on Theatres, 1925-1926 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Telephone: Charges, Changes, Installations, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Treasurer's Office
    - 1928 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 41)
- Plays and productions, 1925-1968; Series VII
  - Acting Record (Yearly), 1932-1964 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Acting: Rehearsal Hours, 1932-1965 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Acting by Weeks, 1932-1966 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Advertising
    - 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Advertising for J.B., 1958 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Advertising Productions
    - 1949-1955 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Advertising, Public Performances, 1927-1936 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Advertising, Show, 1952-1958 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Advertising Rate Cards, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Aubry, Marcel: Jean Cocteau's Agent in USA, Knights of the Round Table Production, 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Audience, Miscellaneous Information, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Audience: Play Notices, Form Letters, 1925-1947 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - 1944-1949 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Attendance (Reports), 1955 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Box Off ice: Faust, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Statements, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Brussels: J.B. Production, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Brussels and European Defense Tour, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Business Management, undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Casts, 1964-1965 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Clearances for Plays, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Clearances: 140 Plays
    - 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - 1954 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Contracts, Producing, 1929-1952 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Dramatic Groups: University and Little Theatre Lists, 1929 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Electronic Lighting: Console Demonstration (George Izenour), 1947 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Experimental Productions, 1934-1937 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Fiske, Visit of Mrs.: in Ghosts, 1926 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - "40" Show: Procedure, 1962-1967 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Proposed, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - John Gielgud and Irene Worth Production, 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - "Hosho No" Troupe: Information, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Major Productions
    - 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Moscow Art Theatre Seminars, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - New Yale Theatre, 1925-1931 (Box 62, Folder 42)
    - Building Information, Plans, 1924-1926 (Box 62, Folder 43)
    - Construction of, 1926-1929 (Box 62, Folder 44)
    - Equipment (Lighting), 1926-1928 (Box 62, Folder 45)
    - Seating Plan, Equipment, Articles, 1924-1937 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - One Acts, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Opera Project, 1944-1948 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Operations Manual: Acting Monitor, 1960-1962 (Box 62, Folder 49)
    - Costume Lists, undated (Box 62, Folder 50)
    - Historical Productions, undated (Box 62, Folder 51)
    - House Manager, 1942-1947 (Box 63, Folder 52)
    - Producing One-Act Plays, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 53)
    - Production Manager, undated (Box 63, Folder 54)
    - Scene Designer, undated (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Organization of Production, 1946, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - Play Festivals, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 57)
  - Play Interpretation and Direction, 1935 (Box 63, Folder 58)
  - Play List, undated (Box 63, Folder 59)
  - Play Selection Committee, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 60)
  - Plays: Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes, 1937-1955 (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - Plays: All the Way Home, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 62)
    - Birthday Party: Production Notes, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 63)
    - The Bridge, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 64)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra: Production Report, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 65)
    - The Castle, 1963-1965 (Box 63, Folder 66)
    - Charlev's Aunt, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 67)
    - Coriolanus: General Info, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 68)
    - Dynamite Tonight, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 69)
    - Enrico IV, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 71)
    - Faust, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 72 - 74)
  - Plays: Hamlet: Promotional Information, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 75)
    - Henry IV, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 76)
      - Collaborative Production by Yale Dramat and Dept. of Drama, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 77)
    - House Afire, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 78)
    - John Brown's Body, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 79)
      - Tour, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 80)
      - Annapolis, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 81)
      - New York, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 82)
      - Yale Club, New York, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 83)
      - Washington, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 84)
    - Little Murders, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 85)
    - Mac Bird, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 86)
      - Reviews, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 87)
    - Man of Distinction, 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 88)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 89)
    - Misalliance, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 90)
    - My Dear Children: Financial Records, 1939-1941 (Box 65, Folder 91)
    - Play of Daniel, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 92)
    - Prometheus/Merchant, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - Prometheus Bound, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 94)
      - General Information, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 95)
      - Actors Equity, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 96)
      - Casting, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 97)
      - Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 98)
      - Physical Production, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 99)
      - Press and Programs, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 100)
      - Publicity, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 101)
      - Reviews, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 102)
    - Rosamunde, 1928-1929 (Box 66, Folder 103)
    - S.S. Glencairn: General Information, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 104)
    - Tartuffe, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 105)
    - Telemachus Clay, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 106)
    - The Three Sisters, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 107)
    - Tis Pitv She's a Whore, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 108)
    - Victor/Viet Rock, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 109)
    - Viet Rock: Contracts, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 110)
      - General Information, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 111)
      - Publicity, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 112)
    - We Bombed in New Haven, 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 117)
      - Opening Night, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 118)
      - Reviews, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 119)
      - Script, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 120)
    - War Period, 1935-1944 (Box 67, Folder 121)
    - Yale Series of Long Plays, 1930-1935 (Box 67, Folder 122)
    - Yale Series of One-Act Plays
      - 1924-1933 (Box 67, Folder 123)
      - 1934-1942 (Box 67, Folder 124)
  - Plays, List of, 1925-1932 (Box 67, Folder 125)
  - Possibilities for Playwrights, 1934-1935 (Box 67, Folder 126)
  - Posters, Announcements, Notices, 1929-1949 (Box 67, Folder 127)
  - Posters of Yale Drama School Productions, undated (Box 67, Folder 128)
  - Prize Plays, 1947-1952 (Box 67, Folder 129)
  - Producing, Opportunities for, 1925-1931 (Box 67, Folder 130)
  - Production Activity, 1946-1947 (Box 67, Folder 131)
  - Production Assignments and Rating Systems, 1957-1959 (Box 67, Folder 132)
  - Production Expenses, 1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 133)
  - Production Management: Activity Records, 1930-1938 (Box 68, Folder 134)
    - Cost Summaries, 1934-1936 (Box 68, Folder 135)
    - "Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme", 1937 (Box 68, Folder 136)
    - Operations Forms (Box 68, Folder 137)
    - Production Work, Hours/Show, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 138)
    - Rehearsal Hours/Show, 1938, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 139)
    - Weekly Schedules, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 140)
    - Yearly Production Work Records, 1928-1963 (Box 68, Folder 141)
  - Production Management Schedules: Individual Shows, 1946-1947 (Box 68, Folder 142)
    - Yearly, 1933-1963 (Box 68, Folder 143)
  - Production Manager's Report
    - Division II, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 144)
    - Division I, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 145)
    - Division II, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 146)
    - Division III, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 147)
    - Division I, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 148)
    - Division II, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 149)
    - Division III, 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 150)
    - Division IV, 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 151)
    - Division I, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 152)
    - Division II, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 153)
    - Division III, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 154)
    - Division IV, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 155)
    - Division I, 1963-1964 (Box 68, Folder 156)
    - Division II, 1963-1964 (Box 68, Folder 157)
    - Division III, 1963-1964 (Box 68, Folder 158)
    - Division IV, 1963-1964 (Box 69, Folder 159)
    - Division I, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 160)
    - Division II, 1964-1966 (Box 69, Folder 161)
    - Division III, 1964-1967 (Box 69, Folder 162)
    - Division IV, 1964-1968 (Box 69, Folder 163)
    - Division II, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 164)
    - Division III, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 165)